University of Aberdeen
Abertay University
Aberystwyth University
Anglia Ruskin University, Cambridge
Arden University, private
Aston University, Birmingham
Bangor University
University of Bath
Bath Spa University
University of Bedfordshire, Luton and Bedford
University of Birmingham
Birmingham City University
University College Birmingham
Bishop Grosseteste University
University of Bolton
The Arts University Bournemouth
Bournemouth University
BPP University
University of Bradford
University of Brighton
University of Bristol
Brunel University, Uxbridge and London
University of Buckingham, private
Buckinghamshire New University, High Wycombe
University of Cambridge
Canterbury Christ Church University, Canterbury
Cardiff Metropolitan University 
Cardiff University
University of Chester, Chester and Warrington
University of Chichester
Coventry University
Cranfield University
University for the Creative Arts, Canterbury, Epsom, Farnham, Maidstone and Rochester
University of Cumbria, Carlisle (main campus), London, Penrith and Ambleside
De Montfort University, Leicester
University of Derby
University of Dundee
Durham University, Durham and Stockton-on-Tees
Earlham Hall at the University of East Anglia
University of East Anglia, Norwich
University of East London
Edge Hill University, Ormskirk, Lancashire
University of Edinburgh
Edinburgh Napier University
University of Essex, Colchester and Southend-on-Sea
University of Exeter
Falmouth University
University of Glasgow
Glasgow Caledonian University
University of Gloucestershire, Cheltenham, Gloucester and London
Glyndŵr University, Wrexham
University of Greenwich
Harper Adams University, Newport, Shropshire
Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh and Galashiels
University of Hertfordshire, Hatfield
University of the Highlands & Islands, Inverness 
University of Huddersfield, Huddersfield & Barnsley
University of Hull, Hull and Scarborough
Imperial College London
Keele University, Staffordshire
University of Kent, Canterbury and Medway
Kingston University
University of Central Lancashire, Preston and Burnley
Lancaster University
University of Leeds
Leeds Beckett University
Leeds Trinity University
University of Leicester
University of Lincoln, Lincoln, Hull, Riseholme and Holbeach
University of Liverpool
Liverpool Hope University
Liverpool John Moores University
University of London
Birkbeck, University of London
City, University of London
Royal Central School of Speech and Drama
Courtauld Institute of Art
Goldsmiths, University of London
Heythrop College
Institute of Cancer Research
King's College London
London Business School
London School of Economics and Political Science (LSE)
London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine
Queen Mary, University of London
Royal Academy of Music
Royal Holloway, University of London, Egham
Royal Veterinary College
St George's, University of London
School of Oriental and African Studies (SOAS)
University College London (UCL)
London Metropolitan University
London South Bank University
Loughborough University
University of Manchester
Manchester Metropolitan University
Middlesex University, London
Newcastle University
Newman University, Birmingham
University of Northampton
Northumbria University, Newcastle upon Tyne
Norwich University of the Arts
University of Nottingham
Nottingham Trent University
The Open University, Milton Keynes 
University of Oxford
Oxford Brookes University
University of Plymouth
University of Portsmouth
Queen Margaret University, Edinburgh
Queen's University Belfast
University of Reading
Regent's University London
The Robert Gordon University, Aberdeen
Roehampton University, London
Royal Agricultural University, Cirencester
University of Salford
University of Sheffield
Sheffield Hallam University
University of South Wales, merger of University of Wales, Newport and University of Glamorgan
University of Southampton
Southampton Solent University
University of St Andrews
University of St Mark & St John, Plymouth
St Mary's University, Twickenham
Staffordshire University, Stoke-on-Trent, Stafford and Lichfield
University of Stirling, Bridge of Allan
University of Strathclyde, Glasgow
University of Suffolk, Ipswich, Bury St Edmunds, Great Yarmouth, Lowestoft
University of Sunderland
University of Surrey, Guildford
University of Sussex, Falmer and Brighton
Swansea University
Teesside University, Middlesbrough and Darlington
University of the Arts London
Ulster University, Coleraine, Jordanstown, Magee and Belfast
University of Law
University of Wales, Trinity Saint David (UWTSD)
University of Warwick, Coventry
University of the West of England, Bristol
University of the West of Scotland, Paisley, Hamilton, Ayr & Dumfries
University of West London, Ealing and Brentford
University of Westminster, London
University of Winchester
University of Wolverhampton
University of Worcester
University of York
York St John University
ifs University College, London
University College of Estate Management, Reading
Writtle University College